Pelke, Bill; Papers apap205
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Amnesty International, 1988-2000, Undated; 4; 3.75 cubic feet
  - National Weak of Student Action, 2000 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 85)
  - Newsletter, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 86)
  - Newsletter, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 87)
  - Newsletter, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 88)
  - Newsletter, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 89)
  - Newsletter, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 90)
  - Newsletter, 1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 91)
  - Newsletter, 2000 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 92)
  - News Release, 1994-1996; 1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 93)
  - Ohio/ Indiana Area Meeting Schedule, Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 94)
  - On the Internet, Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 95)
  - Open Letter to the President on the Death Penalty, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 96)
  - Packet, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 97)
  - Personal Courage and Conscience, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 98)
  - Philippines: The Death Penalty, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 99)
  - Policy and Guidelines on Cooperative Activities Between Amnesty International and the Human Rights Movement, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 100)
  - Poster Draft, circa 1991 (Oversize 8, Folder 3)
  - Preventing the Imposition of the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 101)
  - Protection of Persons, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 1)
  - Public Identification with AI and Cooperation with Outside Groups, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 2)
  - Publications Catalogue, 1995; 1998-1999 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 3)
  - Questionnaire for Mission Delegates, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 4)
  - Ratification Now!, Undated (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 5)
  - Refugee Issues World Conference on Human Rights, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 6)
  - Readings for Human Rights, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 7)
  - Relief Policies and Procedures, Undated (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 8)
  - Religious Action, 1993; 1992 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 9)
  - Report of Local Group Activity, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 10)
  - Report of Death Penalty Legislation in the United States of America, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 11)
  - Rights for All, 1998 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 12)
  - Scaling the Wall, Undated (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 13)
  - Speakers List, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 14)
  - Special Initiatives Fund, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 15)
  - State Death Penalty Action Coordinators Folder, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 16)
  - State Death Penalty Abolition Coordinators, Undated (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 17)
  - Statements for the Mumia Abu - Jamal Speak Out, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 18)
  - Statute of Amnesty International, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 19)
  - Stickers and Bumpber Stickers, Undated (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 20)
  - Summer Postcard Action, 1993; 1996-1998 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 21)
  - Taiwan - Ill - Treatment in Death Row, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 22)
  - Texas and the USA, 1997 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 23)
  - Tip of the Month, Undated (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 24)
  - Trainer Address and Phone List, Undated (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 25)
  - Trainer's Handbook, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 26)
  - Training of Trainers Program, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 27)
  - The Truth about the Death Penalty in the United States in Real News, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 28)
  - Upcoming Anti - Death Penalty Action, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 29)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 30)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 31)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 32)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 33)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 34)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 35)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1997 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 36)
  - Urgent Action Network Survey, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 37)
  - Urgent Action Newsletter, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 38)
  - Urgent Action Newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 39)
  - Urgent Action Newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 40)
  - Urgent Action Telegram Pledge Program, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 41)
  - USA The Death Penalty and Juvenile Offenders, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 42)
  - USA The Death Penalty Briefing, 1987 (Box 3 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 43)
  - Voices, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 1)
  - Voices for Freedom, Undated (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 2)
  - Voter Involvement Form, 1993; 1996-1997 (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 3)
  - Western Region Human Rights Education Institute, 1997 (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 4)
  - Western Regional Conference, 1992; Undated (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 5)
  - When the State Kills, 1989 (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 6)
  - Who's Who, 1995 (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 7)
  - Women's Day Action, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 8)
  - Women's Day Activists, 1997 (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 9)
  - World Conference Vol I, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 10)
  - World Conference Vol II, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 11)
- National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1988-1999, Undated; 5; 1.23 cubic feet
  This series documents Bill Pelkes involvement in National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP). Items included in this series include documents related to Bill Pelkes role as a board member, newsletters, conference documents, flyers, pamphlets, and other outreach materials collected by Bill Pelke.
  - The Abolotionist's Directory, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 1)
  - The Abolotionist's Directory, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 2)
  - Administrative, 1989 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 3)
  - Administrative, 1990 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 4)
  - Administrative, 1991 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 5)
  - Administrative, 1992 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 6)
  - Administrative, 1993 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 7)
  - Administrative, 1995 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 8)
  - Administrative, 1996 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 9)
  - Administrative, 1996 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 10)
  - Administrative, 1997 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 11)
  - Administrative, 1997 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 12)
  - Administrative, 1997 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 13)
  - Administrative, 1998 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 14)
  - Administrative, 1998 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 15)
  - Administrative, 1998 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 16)
  - Administrative, 1999 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 17)
  - Annual Conference, 1990 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 18)
  - Annual Conference, 1991 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 19)
  - Annual Conference, 1992 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 20)
  - Annual Conference, 1993 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 21)
  - Annual Conference, 1994 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 22)
  - Annual Conference, 1995 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 23)
  - Annual Conference, 1996 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 24)
  - Annual Conference, 1997 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 25)
  - Annual Conference, 1998 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 26)
  - Annual Conference, 1999 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 27)
  - Bumper Sticker, Undated (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 28)
  - Case Statement, 1991 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 41)
  - The Death Penalty: The Religious Community Calls for Abolition, Undated (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 42)
  - Declaration of Life, 1997 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 43)
  - Execution Statistics, 1990-1991; 1993-1994 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 44)
  - Facing an Execution Guidelines, Undated (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 45)
  - General, 1988; 1991-1992; 1994; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 46)
  - " Human Rights and Human Wrongs " - report, 1997 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 47)
  - LifeLines, May-October, 1990 (Oversize 8, Folder 4)
  - LifeLines, April-December, 1991 (Oversize 8, Folder 5)
  - LifeLines, 1992 (Oversize 8, Folder 6)
  - LifeLines, 1993 (Oversize 8, Folder 7)
  - LifeLines, 1994 (Oversize 8, Folder 8)
  - LifeLines, January-June, 1995 (Oversize 8, Folder 9)
  - LifeLines, 1996 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 48)
  - LifeLines, 1997 (Oversize 8, Folder 10)
  - LifeLines, May-June, 1998 (Oversize 8, Folder 11)
  - LifeLines, November-December, 1998 (Oversize 8, Folder 12)
  - Members Mailing Stickers, Undated (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 49)
  - Midwest Regional Conference, 1990; 1992 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 50)
  - National Execution Alert, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 51)
  - National Execution Alert, 1996 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 52)
  - National Execution Alert, 1997 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 53)
  - National Execution Alert, 1998 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 54)
  - National Execution Alert, 1999 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 55)
  - National Perspectives Portfolio, 1992 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 56)
  - " Nothing Cheap and Soothing about Multiple Executions " - Steven Hawkins and Donald Cabana, Undated (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 57)
  - Pamphlets and Brochures, 1989; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 58)
  - " Public Opinion and the Death Penalty "- report, 1991 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 59)
  - State Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 60)
  - Stop It! Campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 61)
  - Thomas Thompson Case, 1997 (Box 1 (5-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty), Folder 62)
- General Activism, 1984-2000, Undated; 6; 5.08 cubic feet
  This series contains records pertaining to various international, national, regional, state, and local activist organizations, non-profit groups, political parties, and religious organizations concerned with the death penalty and other activism related activities and events. The groups represented are primarily, but not exclusively, concerned with the abolition of the death penalty and prisoner rights. Included in this series are newsletters, correspondence, pamphlets, flyers, mass mailings, as well as a small amount of administrative material for organizations in which Bill Pelke himself was involved, such as the Indiana Coalition Against the Death Penalty (ICADP), the Northwest Indiana Coalition to the Abolish Control Unit Prisons, and the Northern Indiana Coalition Against the Death Penalty. Researchers should be aware that the bulk of this material consists of public outreach materials collected by Bill Pelke.
  - Abolition: Death Penalty News in Mississippi, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 1)
  - Abolitionist Action Committee, 1994-1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 2)
  - Abolitionist Action Committee - Fast and Vigil, 1995-1998 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 3)
  - Abolitionist Action Committee Packet, 1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 4)
  - ACLU, 1984; 1995-1996 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 5)
  - ACLU, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 6)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1995 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 7)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1995 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 8)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1996 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 9)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1996 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 10)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1996 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 11)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 12)
  - ACLU -Race and the Death Penalty: Georgia and the Nation, 1987 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 13)
  - Activism - Brochures and Pamphlets, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 14)
  - Activism - Events, 1989; 1991-1994 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 15)
  - Activism - Events, 1995-1998 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 16)
  - Activism - Events, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 17)
  - Activism - General, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 18)
  - Activism - General, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 19)
  - Activism - General, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 20)
  - Activism - General, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 21)
  - Activism - General, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 22)
  - Activism - General, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 23)
  - Activism - General, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 24)
  - Activism - General, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 25)
  - Activism Merchandise, 1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 26)
  - Activism - Petitions, 1993; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 27)
  - Activism - Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1992-1993; 1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 28)
  - Activism - Pleas for Help, 1993-1999; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 29)
  - Activism - Pleas for Help, 1993-1999; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 30)
  - Activism - Sample / Model Letters, 1991; 1993; 1996-1997; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 31)
  - Alabama Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1992-1993; 1995; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 32)
  - Alabama Prison Project, 1990; 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 33)
  - Alternatives to Violence Project, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 34)
  - American Bar Association - Death Penalty Representation Project Packet, 2000 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 35)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 36)
  - American Friends Service Committee -Forging Justice, 1990 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 37)
  - American Friends Service Committee -Forging Justice, 1991 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 38)
  - American Friends Service Committee - Religious Organizing Against the Death Penalty, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 39)
  - American Friends Service Committee - Religious Organizing Against the Death Penalty - project packet, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 40)
  - The Andrew Lee Jones Fund, 1995; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 41)
  - Baton Rouge Catholic Worker, 1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 42)
  - Baton Rouge Catholic Worker, 1998 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 43)
  - Baton Rouge Catholic Worker, 1998 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 44)
  - Baton Rouge Catholic Worker, 1999 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 45)
  - Blueprint for Social Justice, 1991 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 46)
  - Bill Pelke - Activism, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 47)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Children's Crusade, 1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 48)
  - Bruderhof Communities -The Plough, 1996 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 49)
  - Bruderhof Communities -The Plough, 1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 50)
  - Bruderhof Communities -The Plough, 1998 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 51)
  - Bruderhof Communities -The Plough, 1999 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 52)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Plough Books Catalogs, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 53)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Plough Books Online, 1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 54)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Plough Publishing, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 55)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Just-Us: Voices for Life, 1996 (Oversize 9, Cd 1)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Take My Hand, 1997 (Oversize 9, Cassette 1)
  - CACJ / CPDA Capital Defense Seminar, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 56)
  - Call to Action, 1995-1996; 1998 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 57)
  - Catholics Against Capital Punishment, 1994; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 58)
  - Center for Community Justice, 1993; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 59)
  - The Center for the Homeless, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 60)
  - The Cesar Chavez Catholic Worker House, 1994; 1996 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 61)
  - Cesar Chavez Community House, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 62)
  - Cesar Chavez Foundation, 1994-1996; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 63)
  - Cesar Chavez Foundation, 1994-1996; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 64)
  - Citizens United for Aleternatives to the Death Penalty, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 65)
  - Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (CUADP) - Button, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 10)
  - Coalition Against Indiana Control Units and Prison Abuse, 1994 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 66)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1992 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 67)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1993 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 68)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1994 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 69)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1995 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 70)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1995 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 71)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1996 (Box 1 (6-General Activism), Folder 72)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 1)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 2)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 3)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 4)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 5)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1999 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 6)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1999 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 7)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 2000 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 8)
  - Coalition of Arizonans to Abolish the Death Penalty -CAADP News, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 9)
  - Coalition to Defeat SR - 395, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 10)
  - Committee for Freedom -Human Rights Held Hostage, 1993 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 11)
  - Committee to End the Marion Lockdown, 1993-1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 12)
  - Committee to End the Marion Lockdown -Walkin' Steel, 1992 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 13)
  - Committee to End the Marion Lockdown -Walkin' Steel, 1993 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 14)
  - Committee to End the Marion Lockdown -Walkin' Steel, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 15)
  - Committee to End the Marion Lockdown -Walkin' Steel, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 16)
  - Committee to Stop Execution, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 17)
  - Conneticut Network to Abolish the Death Penallty -Network News, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 18)
  - Covenant House, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 19)
  - Crime Victime Services -Victim Watch, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 20)
  - Crime Victime Services -Victim Watch, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 21)
  - Crime Victime Services -Victim Watch, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 22)
  - Crime Victime Services -Victim Watch, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 23)
  - Crime Victime Services -Victim Watch, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 24)
  - Criminal Justice and Prison Ministry Conference Packet, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 25)
  - Criminal Justice Newsletter, 1990 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 26)
  - CURE - Indiana Chapter, 1991-1993; 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 27)
  - CURE - OhioChapter, 1992 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 28)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California, 1994-1999 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 29)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California -The Sentry, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 30)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California -The Sentry, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 31)